<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chemoinformatics</title>
    <link>https://Takshan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chemoinformatics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://Takshan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Takshan.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Takshan.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Address Soongsil University 369 Sangdo-Ro, Dongjak-Gu, Seoul, Korea (06978)
TEL : +82-2-820-0114 . FAX : +82-2-814-7362 . E-MAIL : oip@ssu.ac.kr
COPYRIGHT© 2021 SOONGSIL UNIVERSITY. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Takshan.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Takshan.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>Welcome !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Takshan.github.io/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Takshan.github.io/members/</guid>
      <description>Update in Progress.. Coming soon please be patient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Takshan.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Takshan.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications  ZikaBase: an integrated ZIKV-human interactome Map database, S Gurumayum, R Brahma, LD Naorem, M Muthaiyan, J Gopal, Virology 514, 203-210 7 2018 Identification of hub genes and pathways in Zika virus infection using RNA-seq data: a network-based computational approach, R Brahma, S Gurumayum, LD Naorem, M Muthaiyan, J Gopal, Viral immunology 31 (4), 321-332 5 2018 Triton X‐114 Fractionated Subcellular Proteome of Leptospira interrogans Shows Selective Enrichment of Pathogenic and Outer Membrane Proteins in the … S Thoduvayil, G Dhandapani, R Brahma, R Devasahayam Arokia Balaya, Proteomics 20 (19-20), 2000170 1 2020 Comparative proteome analysis reveals pathogen specific outer membrane proteins of Leptospira, MGM Gunasekaran Dhandapani¶, Thoduvayil Sikha¶ , Aarti Rana, Rahul Brahma .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Takshan.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Takshan.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research at Chemoinformatics lab , Soongsil University Soongsil University is carrying out convergence research projects beyond the existing interdisciplinary research. We are enhancing the image of the university as a leader in convergence research and education leading to basic and applied technology and advanced technology
 We carry out optimized convergence research tasks of the fourth industrial revolution era ranging from life technology, robot technology, IT, energy, distribution logistics, contents, and train high-fidelity research manpower that will be the hero of the convergence industry in Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Takshan.github.io/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Takshan.github.io/tools/</guid>
      <description>Web Apps publicly avaivbale for use  BEE FARM  Bee Farm an awesome web app to farm bee.
Download BEE FARM
 BEE FARM  Bee Farm an awesome web app to farm bee.
Download BEE FARM
 BEE FARM  Bee Farm an awesome web app to farm bee.
Download BEE FARM
 BEE FARM  Bee Farm an awesome web app to farm bee.
Download BEE FARM</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
